# **Amy Lim Hooi Leng**

## Software Developer

Being a mid-life career switcher with a strong passion towards IT, I have completed a 6-month full-time certification in Software Development Immersive accredited by Nanyang Technological University, with the aspiration to embark on my next career in software development. With over 20 years of experiences managing clients' relationship and office administration, my strengths lie in a strong commitment, curiosity for new knowledge and information, and strong determination to achieve targeted result, and I believe it will be helpful in a team setup.

# **Programming Skills**

- HTML/ CSS
- Javascript
- Node.JS
- React JS
- React Native

- Express JS
- SQL / NoSQL
- Axios
- Deployment

## **Project Experiences**

Nanyang Technological University (6 months full-time)

### Project 1 - SHOPPING LIST

- Programmed a mobile app for users to note down a shopping list, with the ability to delete selected purchased item(s) and to count the number of shopping items left.
- Coded using Javascript (DOM manipulation) and HTML/CSS

## Project 2 - COVID TRACKER

- Programmed a web app for users to see the latest Covid cases based on Age, ICU numbers, local cases, Vaccination status with filtering based on date
- Collaborated with a team of 4 members
- Coded with REACT, NODE.JS with Axios API

#### Project 3 - FOOD SEARCH APP

- Team Project with 4 other teammates
- Project based on N-tier Architecture
- Backend with Express, Sequelize, Postgresql, using HEROKU for deployment
- Frontend with React Native

## **Personal Info**

#### Mobile

+65 9645 6221

#### **Email**

amylimhooileng@hotmail.com

#### LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/amy-lim-4762b3237

#### **Github**

https://github.com/Ocean272

#### **Portfolio**

https://ocean272.github.io/Amy-Portfolio-website/

## **Education**

# SGUnited Skills Programme in Software Developer Immersive

(Synchronous and Asynchronous e-learning) - 17 January - 15 July 2022

#### **Clementi Institute of Commerce**

(Secretarial Practice)

- 1989 1991
- Leaving Certificate

#### **Hua Yi Secondary School**

- 1985 1988
- GCE 'O' Levels

## Hobbies









# Amy Lim Hooi Leng

## Software Developer

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

### Global Hydraulics Pte Ltd - Singapore

2023 - to present Sales Coordinator

Provided sales support for company

- Tracking sales leads
- Coordinating quotes
- Managing customer accounts

## Elka Music School - Singapore

1992 – 2021 (Part-time) Piano Teacher

- Destructured music score for better understanding for learning.
- Translated and interpreted musical ideas to students.
- Motivated higher grades students towards performance with confidence.
- Conducted various brainstorming sessions.
- Paced students in-line with their learning abilities

## **Marco Tack Pte Ltd - Singapore**

1997 – 1999

Manufacturing company that provides solar windows films

Shipping Coordinator (Sales Department)

- Translated documents and communications (English Chinese) between Middle-East clients and Managing Director
- Handled shipping documentations such as Letter of Credit, foreign import and exports documents and arrangement of shipment.

### **Great Eastern Life - Singapore**

1994 – 1996 Life Insurance Company Secretary to General Sales Manager

- Created Powerpoint slides for recruitments and presentations
- Arranged of weekly and monthly meetings
- Kept office equipment orderly and helped agents on various forms submissions.